PHUTHANADOL DHIANTRAVAN

UX/UI Designer

(+66) 86-039-6413



phumthanadol@gmail.com

As a UX/UI & Graphic Designer at Edutech Innovation Co., Ltd., I have contributed to the design and development of an English learning program for children. I work closely with the graphic and development teams to create user-friendly designs that meet user needs and enhance the overall experience. Additionally, I am responsible for producing graphics and illustrations for the program, as well as marketing materials, collaborating with the marketing team to promote the program and foster effective learning and engagement.

Experience

Oct. 2023 - Present

UX/UI & Graphic Designer - Fulltime

Edutech Innovation Co., Ltd.

- Conduct user behavior analyses to design optimal user experiences (UX) for the product.
- Design user interfaces (UI) that connect users to the product.
- Create prototypes to present the product before handing them over to the development team.
- Create illustrations for use within the program to enhance user engagement and visual appeal.
- Design graphic artwork for marketing purposes, including program news banners, website banners, and Facebook ads.

2023 - Present

Freelance

UX/UI Design for Website

Aug. 2021 - Dec. 2021

Character & Graphic Designer - Contact

ChatStick Co.,Ltd.

Jun. 2021 - Aug. 2021

Character Designer - Internship

ChatStick Co..Ltd.

Education

2019 - 2023

King Mongkut's University of Technology Thonburi

B.Sc. (Applied Computer Science-Multimedia) Faculty of Industrial Education and Technology

GPAX: 3.56 - Second Class Honours

2015 - 2019

Bangkok Christian College

Math-Science Classroom

GPAX: 3.49

Skills

- UX/UI Design Figma
- Digital Painting Clip Studio Paint
- Graphic Design / Layout Adobe Illustrator and Photoshop

Languages

- Thai (Native)
- English (Intermediate)